Previously on JoJo's Bizarre Adventure...
What the hell?
Hell yeah!
Now, whole horse, Montana instructed,
stick your fingers all the way up
Polnareff's nose, and then we'll win!
They're out cold from
losing all that blood!
Lucky you, whole horse!
This is your chance to
finish them off for good!
So, what is this so-called
channel supposed to get here?
And what do I do till then?
Excuse me? Hold on, sir.
What the hell are you doing?
You're not the only one who wants
the answer to that question.
What's the matter, Polnareff?
Shit, what now?
They're on me like white on rice.
Damn it.
How the hell do I make the rest of
this stupid prediction come true?
Hey, Polnareff.
Did you find the person
tailing us? Say something.
After all of the elders,
we'll be here soon!
Dammit!
How am I gonna get out of this one?
Chariot!
Hold it right there!
This is bad! I...
I'm the fastest quick draw around!
Now don't move or you're dead! Hey!
Did you say something?
Hold it, ref!
Hold around!
Hang on.
You've been here the
entire time. What's wrong?
Did you find someone following us or not?
Well...
This is getting uglier by the second.
They've backed me into a corner.
According to that full comic book?
I was supposed to give my big chance.
After I stuck my fingers
up Polnareff's nose!
But everything has gone south.
And I'm about to be in a
whole world of trouble.
I don't know.
The period of one
Stop! Good job!
The beginning of the story.
The moment of the story.
The end of the story.
I'm going to keep going!
The Crusaders.
The last page in the last page.
End of the world.
That's the memory of the blood?
I think I'm gonna cry.
Had I known something like
this was gonna happen,
I would've just blown
him away from a distance.
Mondatta, this is all
your fault, you know that?
That fool Polnareff's sword would've
had nothing on my gun. Damn it.
Polnareff?
You waiting for an invitation?
Tell the scram.
Because I swear to you, Polnareff, if I'm
found out, I'm taking you down with me.
I...
I was wrong.
No one was tailing us.
Guess it was just my imagination.
I see.
And is there any particular reason you're
nonchalantly standing
in the corner like that?
Tell him that you wanted to
find a place to take a leak.
Do it, or I'll put a bullet in your head.
Oh, I had to take a whiz and
couldn't find a toilet, so...
what can you do?
Are you serious?
Come on, you were peeing in the street?
Even after all this time,
your lack of shame amazes me.
For the love of, stop jabbing
that stupid gun into my head!
Wait, I may have found a way out of this.
I'll give them a signal and
hope to God they figure it out.
Look where my tongue is pointing!
Seriously, people!
I'm trying to give you a sign!
Look behind me! Hmm?
Behind me, dammit!
Look behind me!
Shit!
Why'd they stop talking?
Well, as you can see, there's nothing strange
going on here, so you can go on ahead.
Hmm?
All right.
I was lying!
How are you not catching on? My tongue!
Look at my tongue!
He's right behind me!
Please don't leave!
Are you sure you're okay?
You're making a creepy face.
Something wrong with your tongue?
No.
That's not it.
He's trying to tell us that
there's something behind...
Shut your mouth!
You mean...
Damn it, Polnareff.
You low-down dirty son of a...
You were gluing him in!
You've pissed me off for the last time!
I've had just about
enough of you! Now, die!
What the...
Huh?
What's he doing here? Why?
You idiot!
You had to sneeze?
Everyone watch out.
Whole Horse is back and he's got a friend
hiding under the crate so be careful.
Blast it this can't be happening.
He sneezed because I wouldn't
jab my fingers up his nose.
Damn damn if Polnareff
hadn't sneezed the very
least I could have gotten
rid of him for good.
I should have known better than to
team up with the likes of you Mondatta.
Now they're gonna kill me!
This is all happening because
of that blasted premonition!
Now, I'm doomed!
Hey, bro, you seeing what I'm seeing?
It looks like that jackass
that picked a fight with us.
That's him, all right.
I'll never forget the face of
the bastard that blew my ear off.
I'll run him over like
a piece of roadkill!
No!
What?
Seriously?
It all happened so fast,
they didn't have a
chance to whip out their
stands and stop the truck
from running them down!
My fingers went up his nose
and the prediction came true!
I can't believe this!
I got all four of them at once!
It's fate.
My premonitions are always right.
However, it's too soon for
you to finish them off.
We must wait for the next
prediction to be revealed, yes.
Okay!
We did it! They proclaimed.
The chance to finish off
their enemies had arrived.
But be careful, you two.
Don't rush in. Hide and wait.
It's still too soon for us to move in.
Three of them were knocked
out, but Jotaro's still awake.
He's gonna get up any second now.
Jotaro wasn't hit head on by the
truck like Joseph and the others were.
That was close.
If we tried creeping up to him, there's
a chance he could have laid us out.
Great, he's looking for me.
Probably wondering why I
split instead of blowing his
head clear off when I thought
he was down for the count.
We are gonna be able to
beat these yahoos right
we've made it this far
after all i have to win
No matter what it takes
you got that are you
with me mondata yeah we're
so close i can taste it
Mondata it's time to
take these guys out once
and for all so what's our next move you've
proven That your comics
predictions are 100
accurate i was wrong but i believe in you
now and i'll do Whatever i must need me to
stick my fingers up
something i will need me
to eat crap I'll do it without a second
thought i have to win
this fight no matter what
It's here it finally appeared. Yes,
it's the final prediction
what the time has
arrived Whole horse's next
attack will be his last.
While waiting to strike, whole horse came
across two plumbers repairing drain pipes.
He saw the perfect opportunity to win.
and paid them to open one of the pipes.
If Whole Horse were to fire
every last one of his bullets
into that pipe exactly as
the clock struck 12 noon...
Hey, check that out.
Looks like there was a car
accident around the corner.
Who cares about that?
Let's hurry and finish this thing.
Here, hold this pipe for me. Okay.
Wh-what's exactly gonna happen if
I fire my gun into that pipe, huh?
Come on, turn the damn page, would ya?
I know I fire my gun into the
pipe, but what happens after that?
Once they're fired, the bullets go
through the pipe and out the other end.
Kaboom!
Hull Horse's bullets hit their mark and
fly straight through Jotaro's skull!
Right smack in the middle of his forehead!
Yes, yes!
It's finally happening, yes!
Our time's come, yes!
I've been waiting for this since
my brother's accident, yes!
That's great, Mondatta!
I mean, it looks great, but hold on a sec.
Let's make sure we give it a thorough
once-over so we don't get our bacon cooked.
What's happening on this page?
Hey, this is the prediction from when
your brother tried to wipe out Jotaro.
But in the end, your brother was
the one who got himself blown up.
Yeah, but my brother transformed himself
into Jotaro without giving it any thought.
If he hadn't, the prediction
would have come true, yes.
But that's not going to happen to us
because you and I can't transform ourselves.
Yes.
Oh, yeah, you're right.
I don't have changing powers, so I couldn't
pretend to be Jotaro if I wanted to.
Wait, then does that mean...
It does indeed, yes!
At last I can avenge my brother, yes!
There's absolutely no way to
misinterpret this prophecy, yes!
All you have to do is shoot
your bullets into this pipe,
and Jotaro will meet his maker, yes!
Let's back up a bit.
It gave us a specific
time to do it, right?
It's gotta be done by the stroke of noon.
Hey!
Your magic prediction comic
book neglected to mention
we only have two minutes
left before 12 o 'clock!
Don't panic!
All you have to do is
aim your gun and fire!
Yes, you have more than enough time!
Yes, just believe in fate!
It'll work itself out!
Yeah, I know, I know!
It's 100 %!
I believe you, I really do, but...
We're down to the wire
and time's against us!
I've got a whole ass!
You there, worker guys, listen up!
This is a matter of life and death!
I need one of you to open
that pipe on the double!
Just do it, alright?
Hey, who exactly do you think
you're barking orders at?
Who do you think you are, pal?
I'll take a hike.
Yeah, open the pipe, or
you can die! Pole Horse,
you should know that ordinary people
don't have the ability to see your stand.
Yes. Huh?
Huh?
According to the premonition in the
comic, you're supposed to pay the workers.
Yes.
Pay them?
Only a minute, 10 seconds
left before showtime.
All right, all right.
Sorry about the attitude.
I'll pay you to open the pipe,
but you have to do it now.
Please.
Now you're gonna pay us?
Weirdo, why would you give
us money to open the pipe?
Does it really matter?
Hand over what you got.
Yeah, okay.
Yo, what's the holdup, man?
A flap broke!
No, that's right!
I left my wallet at the hotel!
What's with this guy?
Mondatta!
Remember the money I gave to you just
in case you ended up getting lost?
Well, I need you to give it back to
me, so fork it over now, Mondatta!
Right, let's see.
Crap!
We've only got 40 seconds left!
Move your ass!
Uh...
I-I don't know if this is
enough, but go ahead and take it!
Ah!
Whooo!
Hey, I think I saw one of
them roll behind the bricks.
They're just coins, but
there are a lot of them.
Nice.
Must be at least 20 pounds.
Hey, man, watch your feet.
You're steppin' on one.
What's that?
Ah!
Pick up the damn coins later!
You can have them all, okay?
Here you go, boys.
It's getting close to noon.
I made you boys some tea, so take
a load off and have some lunch.
Oh, sounds good to me.
Listen, Granny, I found
them first, so get lost!
Thank you very much, ma 'am.
Put them down!
I told you to hurry up and open the pipe!
If you don't, I'll crack your skulls!
It's open!
Move it!
Now die, Jotaro!
I won!
Just like the predictions said, I shot
the cocky bastard at the stroke of noon!
Go get him!
Old man, time to get up.
I don't think there's
any permanent damage.
I only have cuts and bruises.
But Polnareff, on the other hand...
Hey, don't mean to be a nuisance, but...
Could someone get this
damn thing off of me?
I won!
This is really gonna happen!
Tojoro's right in front of that pipe!
Huh? Ah, shoot!
What?!
Watch it.
Sorry about that, Jotaro.
I don't know what Whole
Horse was thinking!
But he decided sticking
his fingers on my nose?
would be the perfect way
to spend the evening.
That guy is très disgusting.
And my nose still itches.
So sorry again.
But how's it possible?
My bullet's missed!
What the hell?
Were you trying to pull one over on me?
What the hell is going on around here?
I have no idea, yes.
Like I said, my predictions
always come true. It's fate.
I can't believe it.
Not once since I started using my stand
have my predictions ever been wrong.
Well, clearly there's a first time for
everything because they're still alive.
Not a single bullet hit his mark.
It's safe to say your
prediction was totally wrong.
Damn you.
Thanks for joining us
for today's broadcast.
Be sure to tune in next time.
Now for the 12 o 'clock news.
Huh?
What the hell?
There's no way in hell
it's just now, Noon.
I know what happened.
My watch is...
My watch is fast.
And that means I ended up firing
off the bullets before it was time.
But now it is, Noon.
What's that mean for us, huh?
Tell me, what the hell's going to happen
to us now that we've gone off script?
No, it can't be.
But where do we get off track?
It said the bullets will go right through
Joe Tarot's forehead
at the stroke of noon.
Hall Horse, the bullets are...
Come on!
All I need to know is
what's going to happen next!
Hey, tell me I'm not the only one
who heard that ear-piercing scream.
I'm not clear on the details, but
there's something fishy going on here.
But the bigger concern is this truck.
I think we'd better get out of here
before the cops start showing up.
Let's move, man.
But before we go, I want to know where
Whole Horse ran off to. I don't know.
He disappeared for some reason.
Hey, if you don't get away from that
pipe, you're going to get soaking wet.
You should try to be more careful.
Is he dead?
No, but he's critical.
I couldn't even begin to tell
you what transpired here today.
They looked him over and it
seems as though the bullet
went through his forehead
and out the top of his head.
One centimeter lower, and
he would have been a goner.
Oof.
Gotta say, that is one lucky man.
In the end, it seems my
prediction was right.
Which means this was Whole
Horse's fate all along.
Jojo is really something else.
How lucky can one person be?
Both my brother and Whole
Horse were defeated by fate.
At this point, we stand
users are wasting our time.
Master Days, the only
one who can defeat him.
You know what, Zenyatta?
Whole Horse, that big buffoon of a man,
taught me that revenge is
nothing more than a massive joke.
So, I'm going to forget about Jotaro.
I have a new path in life.
I'll use my stand's powers to
help as many people as I can.
I'll use them to bring
happiness to everyone.
Maybe people will start to like us.
And just maybe our
future will be brighter.
I'm tired of being afraid.
Today's the last day I spend under
a box cowering from everyone.
I learned a lot from this battle.
More than I thought I could.
I'm coming home now, brother.
I'm coming home to ask one to join you.
Huh? Huh?
Oh my gosh, I am so sorry.
I kicked it without thinking.
I didn't mean to hit you.
Please forgive me. Hold on.
This dog, he looks familiar.
I'm pretty sure I've seen him before.
But where?
Ah!
There's no way!
It can't be!
No!
Hey, now that I think about
it, where'd our dumbass dog go?
You're talking about Iggy?
I'm sure he's scrounging
around for food somewhere.
I've said from the beginning he
wouldn't help us when we needed him.
He should have known it
wouldn't be so simple.
If people could change that
easily, life wouldn't be so hard.
So as fate would have it, Mondatta
joined Whole Horse in the hospital.
Only now, he was meager than ever before.
But, um...
Do you believe it?
I believe it!
Hell Horse! Bang! Compa!
I'm the player of the Hall Horse.
The card's name is Emperor.
I'm going to fight with the two-man.
I'm going to fight with someone.
But you're okay with this?
I'm a Boingo man.
I'm a Bang
-go man.
It's 100 %!
But this is how it's going to work?
I don't have to believe it's
going to be a good idea.
The fact that you're going to
print out is the best thing.
It's the best thing.
The fact that you're going
to be the best thing.
If you're going to do it,
it's all going to work.
You're going to believe it.
First!
Hot Horse, Boingo, Combi!
I believe, yes!
OK, I believe!
Hot Horse, Boingo, Combi!
The truth is that I can't read correctly!
I have a soft spot for kid dog lovers.